They kidnapped his son. Big mistake.
Seized is a action, thriller, adventure film directed by Isaac Florentine.
Hiding out with his son Taylor on the Mexican coast, Nero hopes to
put his violent Special Forces career behind him.
But after Nero’s home is attacked and Taylor is abducted, the mysterious Mzamo
orders Nero to slaughter the members of three rival crime syndicates.
If he fails, Taylor will die.
Now, with bullets flying and bodies dropping as Nero completes his
mission, he races to find Mzamo’s hideout and seek revenge.
Nero, played by Scott Adkins.
Mzamo, played by Mario Van Peebles.
Taylor, played by Matthew Garbacz.
Donovan, played by Steven Elder.
Walker, played by James P. Bennett.
Alanza, played by Karlee Perez.
Seized is a 2020 American action thriller film directed by Isaac Florentine.
The film stars Scott Adkins and Mario Van Peebles and follows the former special agent who must eliminate
three crime syndicates of highly skilled criminals in exchange for his son who is kidnapped.
The tone is dark and intense.